[{"answer": "NIDENTIFIED FEMALE: No.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 25, "question": "Did the president call?", "qSentId": 24}, {"answer": "I was told not to communicate with them.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Why did you wait so long to tell them?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Well, the family was prepared for George Zimmerman getting a bail.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "And also to his public apology?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Well, the apology is for the family.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "I mean, can you really blame him for wanting to do what everyone's been screaming at him to do?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Well, this family has said all along that they have full faith in the justice system.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "Are they prepared for that eventuality?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "Well, it was a discretionary call by the judge.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Would you have expected that knowing Florida law as you do?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Piers, I have been in a legal community in Miami for well over 20 years.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Do you agree with what he just said?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Well, I don't really agree with at least the last commentator.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "I mean, what did you make of what they were saying?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I was really sort of shocked watching this hearing.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "Would you be confident if you were defending George Zimmerman now from everything you've seen, read, and heard?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "Well, it may be they're holding it back.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "What's your gut tell you?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "How do you expect a judge to do a decent job in making a ruling when you don't give him any evidence?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Well, I'm -- you know, I -- I can't -- I feel that the pain, you know, that the family is going through.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "What do you feel about it?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Well, I -- what I think is the laws are - the rules are old.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "Do you think that George Zimmerman was a racist who targeted Trayvon because he was black?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it's probably an old stigma also because you got to look at the -- you know, the way our country was built.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "First of all, thank goodness that I stayed alive.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "When you wrote the book, what are your feelings when you finished it towards the officers who did what they did to you that day 21 years ago?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Have you forgiven, in your mind, the policemen that did what they did?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Going forward?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "I have much respect for them, much respect.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "How do you feel now about the police?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "I love the way you were laughing so uncomfortably at yourself dancing there.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "Well, I mean, could you imagine if you were dancing like that?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "Pretty much, yes.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Oh, it is?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Hardly.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "Do you still look on scenes like that with great affection or does it become this terrible curse you wish you'd ever been involved with?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "\"Seinfeld\"?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "I think I never really caught up to how big -- honestly to how big it was until right before we ended.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "At moment when you first start making (INAUDIBLE), at what moment do you start thinking -- actually this could be huge?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "I swear to you.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "I don't remember.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Didn't like 100 million people watch that?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "It was like a Super Bowl, yes.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "If I'm exaggerating, go with me.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "Do we have a fact checker here?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "We get together on a daily basis.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "Do you have like little \"Seinfeld\" reunions in some dingy little bar in Manhattan?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "We do see each other on occasion.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "Do the ships just pass out of the port and that's it?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's a couple things.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "What is it about that show, do you think?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Yes, we're going to have to now.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Don't you have a bleeper here?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "I have more sympathy for all women in government.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "Did you have more or less sympathy for her by the end of your process, just on what it takes to be a vice president?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "No, not more Sarah Palins in my opinion.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "More Sarah Palins?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Well, it's interesting because all of these issues are -- trans-vaginal probes and --", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "No, I mean just generally for women in America right now?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "I know.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "Are you expecting some sharp flip-flopping?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "I love it.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "What do you make of your country right now generally?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "I have no idea.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "What is the solution for America?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "For my children, I want my children to be active.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "How are we going to get there?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "That's good.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "What else?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "Yes, it's why you should be running for office.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "You do?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "I would go on the anti-transvaginal probe brigade.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "What office do you think I should run for?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "I'm not sure any part of it.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "What part of that character did he fall in love with?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "Yes, definitely.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "Yeah, you think?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "Well, let's see, first of all, we're separating.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "How have the pair of you, who are in the same profession, managed to stay happily married for 25 years?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "Here's the deal.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 676, "question": "How did you know he was the right guy?", "qSentId": 675}, {"answer": "I do feel lucky.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 690, "question": "Do you feel lucky?", "qSentId": 689}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 698, "question": "Do you make each other laugh?", "qSentId": 697}, {"answer": "No, it's not an \"SNL\" battle.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "Because there's an \"SNL\" battle every day?", "qSentId": 701}, {"answer": "No, I'm kidding.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "Are you seriously about to split up?", "qSentId": 710}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120420pmt", "aSentId": 726, "question": "What could go wrong?", "qSentId": 725}]